<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BPMI UCLA</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BPMI UCLA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A short collection of Pandemic Poems</title>
      <link>/posts/pandemicpoetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pandemicpoetry/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Cheyanne Mclaurin
Email: cheyannem888@gmail.com
Introduction Cheyanne Mclaurin is a port based in Los Angeles, California. She is also currently study at University of California, Los Angeles, as the Class of 2024. For personal interests, Cheyanne loves eating, sightseeing, and working out.
About Artwork The following poems were inspired by the roller coaster of emotions that I and many others have faced during the pandemic. They focus mainly on the ups and down of isolation as well as the process of adjusting to our new world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous love to elsewhere and here</title>
      <link>/posts/anonymouslovetoelsewhereandhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/anonymouslovetoelsewhereandhere/</guid>
      <description>About Author **Artist Name: ** Gabriele Lombardi
Email: gabrielelombardi10@gmail.com
Introduction Gabriele Lombardi is 31 years old, from a small village in the province of Parma, in nothern Italy.
About Artwork My project &amp;ldquo;anonymousloveto&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;elsewhere_and_here&amp;rdquo; aims to document and at the same time restore dignity to people and to the activities to which this dignity has been subtracted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Before Everything</title>
      <link>/posts/beforeeverything/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/beforeeverything/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Taizhi Chen
Email: tchen29@sva.edu
Introduction Taizhi Chen is a student artisit at School of Visual Arts, New York City.
About Artwork On March 3, 2020, between Midtown Manhattan 23rd Street Sixth Avenue and Broadway Street, New York City: During the outbreak of the new coronavirus, I did not see anyone wearing a mask. The flashing red light of the ambulance beside the road reflected from the faces of passers-by, heralding the fate of everyone next year</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona Tea Time</title>
      <link>/posts/coronateatime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/coronateatime/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Sarah Addouh
Email: sarahaddouh@gmail.com
Instagram: @sarahaddouh
Introduction Sarah Addouh is an architect and collage artist based in Morocco, Casablanca.
About Artwork Sarah Addouh took this series of photos during the lockdown in Morocco. It represents sharing while respecting social distancing due to the pandemic. It also shows how we have to be careful in every single task we have to do like serving food or a glass of tea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona Time</title>
      <link>/posts/coronatime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/coronatime/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Zheng Fang
Email: zhengfang19@g.ucla.edu
Introduction Zheng Fang was the youngest person in the world. As the cofounder of 夹山改梁, Zheng Fang starts his journey in the nexus of interactive installation, game design, generative art, performance, experimental video, painting, experimental theater, curation, and education, etc.
After graduating from the Printmaking Department of Central Academy of Fine Arts in 2018, he is now a graduate student majoring in Design | Media Arts, UCLA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID</title>
      <link>/posts/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/covid/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Berna Gulbey
**Instagram:&amp;quot;&amp;quot; https://www.instagram.com/bernagulbey/
Introduction Berna Gulbey has about 50 paintings so far for her COVİD collection.
About Artwork In my COVID series I am aiming to show the effect of this Virus on people from all walks of life, it aims to put a full stop in that moment of time and freezes the emotion of the moment in history.
![All In This Together 2020](../../images/impressions-covid/BPMISubmissions/COVID/All In This Together 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid Artifact</title>
      <link>/posts/covidartifact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/covidartifact/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: James Gouldthorpe
Email: jwgouldthorpe@gmail.com
Introduction I have always been drawn to narrative and even at its most abstract my work suggests a plot. I have found that referencing a story is an effective way to explore my own particular conceptual ideas, and a compelling way to engage an audience. Painting one image often does not fully express the ideas I am exploring, but painting several images and thoughtfully juxtaposing them next each other they begin to create their own visual language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Die for What</title>
      <link>/posts/dieforwhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dieforwhat/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Big Rex
Email: b.rex.contact@gmail.com
Instagram: @big.rex1
Introduction Big Rex is a graphic designer based in Peru. He tries to create and communicate a message of reflection through a stance towards what he sees every day. His ideas are based on playing different stories that take place in the same space in parallel time. His artwork is full of very unique surreal characters which are inspired by everyday life situations, experiences, old magazines, storybooks and ideas about what the future will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Want Cotton Candy?</title>
      <link>/posts/doyouwantcottoncandy_/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/doyouwantcottoncandy_/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Kimberly Giselle
Email: kgutie56@g.ucla.edu
Introduction My work consists of photographing the beauty of nature, capturing the world through my perspective. Nature is peaceful, yet calming to me as it is expressed throughout my work. Although my images depict green sceneries, the desert is also intriguing to me by its appealing view of the silky warm sand. My photographs often reveal the ravishing structure of mother earth, traveling to different locations across California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreakuri Yumi</title>
      <link>/posts/dreakuriyumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dreakuriyumi/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Andi Zhang
Email: 87414045@qq.com
Introduction: Andi is an artist graduated from Central Academy of Fine Arts in China.
About Artwork The work originated from my fear of pandemics and other diseases, drawing on the image of virus-infected cells, cancer cells, blood vessels, and gas masks, and giving the work a &amp;ldquo;breathing&amp;rdquo; effect through programming and new conductive materials. I hope to express the things I fear and the process of defeating my fears in the form of beauty, embodying my own artistic view of life and death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GUARD</title>
      <link>/posts/guard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/guard/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Icy Lu
Email: lyx20031028@gmail.com
Introduction: Icy is a 17-year-old second year undergraduate international student in Los Angeles.
About Artwork This poster was finished in early 2021. In the picture, a doctor with tired eyes silently guards a little girl with his wings. Our current easy life comes from these people who dedicate themselves silently and don&amp;rsquo;t ask for rewards are bearing the burden for us. The tired eyes of the doctor, the faint wrinkles between the eyebrows and the puffiness all revealed the menacing force of the pandemic and the hard work of the medical staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Survive</title>
      <link>/posts/justsurvive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/justsurvive/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Ellen Lee
Email: ellenyealim@gmail.com
About Artwork My piece &amp;ldquo;Just Survive&amp;rdquo; is about how it&amp;rsquo;s enough to simply live. In our society, being productive is seen as our only goal in life. We place so much of our self worth on productivity whether that is with academics, self care, etc. This is one of the reasons why the corona virus pandemic has had such a huge effect on many people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lexie: A Tale During Covid</title>
      <link>/posts/lexieataleduringcovid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/lexieataleduringcovid/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Yingru Huang
Email: yinhua2017@yahoo.com
Introduction Yingru is a senior stutent in UCLA. She started dancing at the age of five, after her parents enrolled her into her local ballet studio, hoping that she will gain some lifelong skills that will carry into her future. What they didn&amp;rsquo;t expect, however, was for her to genuinely pursue dance full-heartedly as both artistic and academic realms of study. After being given dance and choreographic opportunities throughout high school, Yingru affirmed her love for dance as an expressionist medium and studied under UCLA&amp;rsquo;s World Arts and Culture/Dance department to further explore and research her artistic whims.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More PPE Now</title>
      <link>/posts/moreppenow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/moreppenow/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Mildred Grace German
Email: mildredgracegerman@gmail.com
Website: http://www.mildredgracegerman.wixsite.com/website
Introduction Mildred Grace German is a Filipino-Canadian multidisciplinary artist based on the unceded Coast Salish Territories of the Musqueam, Squamish, and Tsleil-Waututh Nations.
About Artwork &amp;ldquo;It was nearly a wipe out of parts of the working class, as nurses, and workers scrambled to find N95, and PPEs. Where were the unions and government agencies in securing these PPE supplies for the workers and the masses, as news of the coronavirus spread months before the lockdown?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Fossils</title>
      <link>/posts/pandemicfossils/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pandemicfossils/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Ken Goldman
Email: ksgoldman2001@yahoo.com
&amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;Website:** www.kengoldmanart.com
Instagram: @kengoldmanart
Introduction Ken Goldman is an artist based in Israel. His art is filled with insider references innuendos and humor. While at times seemingly irreverent - the works are inspired by and react to; traditional, texts, and rituals. He sees his art as a vehicle for promoting dialogue, a catalyst for provoking people into re-evaluating their preconceptions, a medium for breaking down stereotypes, and an opportunity for people of all walks of life to connect with theirs and others&#39; religion, culture, and history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandemonium</title>
      <link>/posts/pandemonium/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pandemonium/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Elisabeth Koch
Email: elikoch@g.ucla.edu
Introduction Elisabeth Koch is a PhD student in Iranian Studies and Egyptology at UCLA, the model her boyfriend, who consented to the submission of this picture despite him sporting a pandemic haircut.
About Artwork This picture was taken in the catacombs of Kom el-Shoqafa in Alexandria, Egypt. It captures the ominous atmosphere that has infused every day life during the pandemic. Death has become as omnipresent as it is in the catacombs, which are part of the necropolis of ancient Alexandria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pickled Stripper - Life Through Pickled Color Glasses</title>
      <link>/posts/pickledstripper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pickledstripper/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Kayla Tange
Email: kaylatange@g.ucla.edu
Website: www.kaylatange.com
Introduction: Kayla Tange was born in South Korea and adopted by a Japanese American family. Her love for poetry and photography slowly progressed into a conceptual performance practice which incorporates elements of exotic dancing. Physical and psychic boundaries, sexuality and permanence are also recurring themes. She often uses dark comedy in her performance work to explore love and longing, societal taboos and catharsis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle</title>
      <link>/posts/seattle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/seattle/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Aaron Zhang
Email: zaaron233@gmail.com
Introduction Aaron Zhang is a junior international student studying at UCSD. In his spare time, he enjoys photography, aerial photography, and video editing.
About Artwork In the first half of the year, the epidemic broke out. Overnight, major cities in the United States seemed to pause. Even during peak hours of traffic congestion in downtown Seattle, there is only a few vehicles on I-5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Heroes | How NOT to Use Masks</title>
      <link>/posts/superheroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/superheroes/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Javier Pérez Estrella
Email: hello@cintascotch.com
Introduction Javier Pérez Estrella is a 35 years old artist from Ecuador.
About Artwork How NOT to Use Masks A funny guide of how NOT to use masks in pandemic.
Super Heroes During the quarantine, he created these illustrations to pay tribute to doctors around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Precaution</title>
      <link>/posts/takingprecaution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/takingprecaution/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Jessica Till
Email: jessicatill@g.ucla.edu
Introduction Jessica Till is a contemporary artist that utilizes various software applications and immersive processes to explore issues of identity. Her passion for digital photography, experimental projection lighting, graphic design, and typography helps her explore social roles and interactions between technology and humanity.
About Artwork In a world where disinformation is more viral than Covid-19 itself, it is important to take all the necessary precautions to protect yourself and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The privilege of quarantine 2020</title>
      <link>/posts/theprivilegeofquarantine2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/theprivilegeofquarantine2020/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Luciana Acuña
Email: acunia.luciana@gmail.com
Introduction Luciana Acuña is an art historian from Argentina, who is also developing photo-documentary and photojournalism that works independently. She also has consolidated experience as a curator and content writer in different national and international media for more than ten years.
About Artwork The current situation in the context of a pandemic led to the fact that, faced with the obligation of compulsory isolation, the structural inequality of my country became evident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sense of Distance - A Production Line of the Shelter</title>
      <link>/posts/thesenseofdistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/thesenseofdistance/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Shiyu Huang
Email: 1511781853@qq.com
About Artwork Shiyu went to the west of Sichuan, China in August 2020. At that time, the pandemic was well controlled, so people tended to pull down the mask and hang it over their chins to breathe the fresh air in the remote mountains. However, Shiyu saw that when people encountered strangers or unfamiliar places, they still wore the mask to show a &amp;ldquo;safe distance&amp;rdquo; from the strangeness and a &amp;ldquo;sense of crisis&amp;rdquo; towards the unknown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOUCH</title>
      <link>/posts/touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/touch/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Marissa Bennett
Email: marissabennett48@gmail.com
Website: https://www.marissaebennett.com
Introduction Marissa Bennett is a multidisciplinary designer based in Los Angeles, California. She specializes in graphic design, illustration, and photography. Marissa recently completed her final year working towards a Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Design Media Arts with a minor in Global Studies at the University of California Los Angeles (UCLA) in June 2020.
About Artwork This work is a revisitation and analysis of images taken while I was living in Italy during the beginning of the COVID-19 outbreak, with an emphasis on photos from a weekend trip to Venice on February 22, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncanny</title>
      <link>/posts/uncanny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/uncanny/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Yuying Song
Email: songyuying0203@hotmail.com
Youtube Video: https://youtu.be/d9slDBMoUcQ
Introduction Yuying Song is currently in Valencia, Spain. She is pursuing a Doctoral degree in Art Production and Research, at the Polytechnic University of Valencia.
About Artwork Affected by the covid-19 epidemic, people&amp;rsquo;s lifestyles has been changed, alcohol and masks have become necessities in people&amp;rsquo;s daily lives. Keeping a safe social distance in public has become the norm in people&amp;rsquo;s lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP: Student Perspectives on COVID-19</title>
      <link>/posts/wakeupstudentperspectivesoncovid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/wakeupstudentperspectivesoncovid-19/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Geneva Hines
Email: geneva.w.hines@ryerson.ca
Introduction Geneva Hines is a media production student from Ryerson University, Toronto, Ontario.
About Artwork Created in summer 2020, the WAKE UP: Student Perspectives On COVID-19 Documentary includes the contributions of 34 students from 12 different countries, representing five continents. The documentary highlights the degree of impact the novel virus has had on a wide range of students.
As COVID-19 has taken the world by storm, one thing has grown increasingly apparent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Without Us</title>
      <link>/posts/withoutus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/withoutus/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Federico Clapis
Email: curator@federicoclapis.com
Introduction: Federico Clapis is a sculpture artist from Milan, Italy.
![Health First, 2020, 83x126x50 cm, mixed media](../../images/impressions-covid/BPMISubmissions/WithoutUS/Health First, 2020, 83x126x50 cm, mixed media.jpg)
![Physical Distancing, 2020, 30x32x34 cm, mixed media](../../images/impressions-covid/BPMISubmissions/WithoutUS/Physical Distancing, 2020, 30x32x34 cm, mixed media.jpg)
![Prison home, 2015, Mixed media,135x30x30 cm](../../images/impressions-covid/BPMISubmissions/WithoutUS/Prison home, 2015, Mixed media,135x30x30 cm.jpg)
![Without us, 2020, 50x40x40 cm, mixed media](../../images/impressions-covid/BPMISubmissions/WithoutUS/Without us, 2020, 50x40x40 cm, mixed media.jpg)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN CALL「Impressions COVID」Online Art Exhibition</title>
      <link>/posts/impressions-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 12:45:05 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/impressions-covid/</guid>
      <description>Important Dates Submission Deadline: January 24th, 2021
Exhibition Opening: February 15th, 2021
Exhibition Portal: 「Impressions COVID」
 About This Exhibit Teeming with natural disasters, domestic and international social tensions, these past few months hardly left us with a mental break.
As a student organization founded amidst the pandemic, we hope to provide a safe space for all to share their perspectives and to document the different experiences in this special time, from the US and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe App Ux Study</title>
      <link>/portfolio/recipe-app-ux-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:19:35 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/recipe-app-ux-study/</guid>
      <description>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consetetur sadipscing elitr, sed diam nonumy eirmod tempor invidunt ut labore et dolore magna aliquyam erat, sed diam voluptua. At vero eos et accusam et justo duo dolores et ea rebum. Stet clita kasd gubergren, no sea takimata sanctus est Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consetetur sadipscing elitr, sed diam nonumy eirmod tempor invidunt ut labore et dolore magna aliquyam erat, sed diam voluptua.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Case Study for Agriculture App</title>
      <link>/portfolio/ux-case-study-for-agriculture-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 12:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/ux-case-study-for-agriculture-app/</guid>
      <description>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consetetur sadipscing elitr, sed diam nonumy eirmod tempor invidunt ut labore et dolore magna aliquyam erat, sed diam voluptua. At vero eos et accusam et justo duo dolores et ea rebum. Stet clita kasd gubergren, no sea takimata sanctus est Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consetetur sadipscing elitr, sed diam nonumy eirmod tempor invidunt ut labore et dolore magna aliquyam erat, sed diam voluptua.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event App Case Study</title>
      <link>/portfolio/event-app-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:07:16 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/event-app-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consetetur sadipscing elitr, sed diam nonumy eirmod tempor invidunt ut labore et dolore magna aliquyam erat, sed diam voluptua. At vero eos et accusam et justo duo dolores et ea rebum. Stet clita kasd gubergren, no sea takimata sanctus est Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consetetur sadipscing elitr, sed diam nonumy eirmod tempor invidunt ut labore et dolore magna aliquyam erat, sed diam voluptua.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study One</title>
      <link>/portfolio/case-study-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/case-study-one/</guid>
      <description>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consetetur sadipscing elitr, sed diam nonumy eirmod tempor invidunt ut labore et dolore magna aliquyam erat, sed diam voluptua. At vero eos et accusam et justo duo dolores et ea rebum. Stet clita kasd gubergren, no sea takimata sanctus est Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consetetur sadipscing elitr, sed diam nonumy eirmod tempor invidunt ut labore et dolore magna aliquyam erat, sed diam voluptua.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
