<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gallery on BPMI UCLA</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gallery on BPMI UCLA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Overview「Impressions COVID」Online Art Exhibition</title>
      <link>/posts/exhibitoverview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/exhibitoverview/</guid>
      <description>Important Dates Exhibition Timeframe: February 15th, 2021 - April 15th, 2021
Exhibition Portal: 「Impressions COVID」
 About This Exhibit Teeming with natural disasters, domestic and international social tensions, these past few months hardly left us with a mental break.
As a student organization founded amidst the pandemic, we hope to provide a safe space for all to share their perspectives and to document the different experiences in this special time, from the US and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Team「Impressions COVID」Online Art Exhibition</title>
      <link>/posts/teaminfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/teaminfo/</guid>
      <description>Our Team We are the Bruin Project Management Initiatives (BPMI) at UCLA, a non-profit organization.
Project Manager
Ophelia Dong
B.S. Statistics, B.A. French, Class of 2022
Website Design
Jack Zhao
B.S. Computer Science, Class of 2021
Artist Contacts
Cora Deng
B.S. Mathematics and Economics, Class of 2022
Xinyi Shen
B.S. Bio-Chemistry, B.A. Communication, Class of 2023
Candice Cai
B.S. Data Theory, Class of 2023
Leonard Zhang
B.S. Financial Actuarial Mathematics, Class of 2022</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children Artworks</title>
      <link>/posts/childrenartworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/childrenartworks/</guid>
      <description>About the Artworks These works have been generously provided by the Kids &amp;amp; Art Foundation.
Artist Name: Galilea &amp;amp; Rachel
&amp;ldquo;Beetle Collage&amp;rdquo;
Galilea created this mixed media collage at the 2019 Google Destination Workshop. Galilea is now cancer free. She was in treatment for Ewing sarcoma at Stanford Children’s Hospital.
Artist Name: Luis &amp;amp; Nathalie
&amp;ldquo;Red Ship 2&amp;rdquo;
Galilea created this mixed media collage at the 2019 Google Destination Workshop. Galilea is now cancer free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnering Charity: Kids &amp; Art Foundation</title>
      <link>/posts/kidsart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/kidsart/</guid>
      <description>About Us Kids &amp;amp; Art Foundation’s mission is to improve the quality of pediatric cancer care by focusing on the whole child in treatment by including healing through arts in their protocol. We seek to improve well-being during treatment, as survivors, and in bereavement. We hold various art workshops for healing, to empower, encourage, and create memorable experiences.
Ways you can help There are many ways you can help in the Kids &amp;amp; Art Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnering Charity: Free Arts</title>
      <link>/posts/freeart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/freeart/</guid>
      <description>About Us Free Arts uses art to restore hope, resilience and self-esteem in children in Los Angeles ages 5-18 who have experienced abuse, poverty, neglect and/or homelessness. The mission, values, and purpose of Free Arts focus on uplifting those most impacted by injustice and inequity in our community. We remain steadfast in this work while continually examining what more we can do, to not only provide services, but to dismantle the structures and systems that stand in the way of equality, inclusion, and opportunity for every single member of society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnering Charity: Children&#39;s Cancer Research Fund</title>
      <link>/posts/childrenresearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/childrenresearch/</guid>
      <description>About Us “We believe a world without childhood cancer is possible – but it’s going to take all of us.” &amp;mdash; Children’s Cancer Research Fund
Children’s Cancer Research Fund supports the brightest scientists whose ideas make the greatest impact for children with cancer. We work closely with researchers to fund innovative new projects quickly so that their promising new discoveries can continue uninterrupted. Our researchers share their findings with more than 9,000 experts around the globe, collaborating with others to accelerate discoveries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(ab)normal</title>
      <link>/posts/abnormal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/abnormal/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Bella Liu
Introduction Bella studies digital media. She enjoys hiphop and loves going to livehouse.
About Artwork Partnering with workers from the bio-art fields, we took photos of microorganisms by using microscopes.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Map of Quarantine</title>
      <link>/posts/amapofquarantine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/amapofquarantine/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Anna Ziser
Introduction Anna Ziser is a student at UCLA, class of 2024.
About Artwork For this project (completed May 2020), I researched the history of cartography and how artists can use maps to represent complex and poetic ideas. Because maps are so critical to helping us feel like we know where we are, I became interested in the idea of being lost, and what makes it unsettling but also valuable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous love to elsewhere and here</title>
      <link>/posts/anonymouslovetoelsewhereandhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/anonymouslovetoelsewhereandhere/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Gabriele Lombardi
Introduction Gabriele Lombardi is 31 years old, from a small village in the province of Parma, in nothern Italy.
About Artwork My project &amp;ldquo;anonymousloveto&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;elsewhere_and_here&amp;rdquo; aims to document and at the same time restore dignity to people and to the activities to which this dignity has been subtracted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baek-il</title>
      <link>/posts/baekil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/baekil/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Heun Jung Kim
About Artwork The traditional Korean “Baek-il” event is a centuries-old tradition considered a norm in many Korean households. This signifies a major milestone within the Korean culture of a child’s 100th day after birth because of the high infant mortality during the 18th Century until the Korean War in the 1950s.
The photograph shows a double portraiture of my younger sister celebrating this milestone with her daughter dressed in the Hanbok during the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Before Everything</title>
      <link>/posts/beforeeverything/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/beforeeverything/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Taizhi Chen
Introduction Taizhi Chen is a student artisit at School of Visual Arts, New York City.
About Artwork On March 3, 2020, between Midtown Manhattan 23rd Street Sixth Avenue and Broadway Street, New York City: During the outbreak of the new coronavirus, I did not see anyone wearing a mask. The flashing red light of the ambulance beside the road reflected from the faces of passers-by, heralding the fate of everyone next year</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Berlins Answer No.6</title>
      <link>/posts/berlinsanswer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/berlinsanswer/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Darren Jones
About Artwork This work is part of a series of pieces called &amp;ldquo;Berlins Answer&amp;rdquo;. Berlin/Germany has a huge underground fetish scene, the gasmasks, latex, bondage etc is in a way detaching from the world or reality, the pandemic has told us to “isolate&amp;quot;. The bondage/sensory deprivation is an isolation, they go hand in hand. Here, l played on these facts, that this is maybe how the fetish community would isolate in another world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break Crisis</title>
      <link>/posts/breakcrisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/breakcrisis/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Saminga (Minjia) Xia
Introduction Saminga received her two bachelor degrees from the Art and Law School of TsingHua University respectively. She also received her master degree from the Art School of Tsinghua University.
About Artwork Break Crisis employs mulberry paper, wool and other natural fibre materials to visualize the infections and morbid state things within our society, our world. We shall take actions to address any &amp;ldquo;sickness&amp;rdquo; caused by infection and deterioration of any kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathe</title>
      <link>/posts/breathe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/breathe/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Spandana Urlam
Introduction Spandana Urlam is a self-taught artist based in India. I am a computer science engineering student but super busy chasing my dream of being a full-time artist. My creative works include Oil paintings, digital paintings and wall murals. I paint anytime, anywhere and pretty much all the time and everywhere. My artworks are usually inspired from travel, music and nature. Living in the process of creation helps me fully own the artwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communication</title>
      <link>/posts/communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/communication/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Xuemei Ge
Introduction I am an artist, also a warrior. I use art as a language and weapon to break free from the shackles that society has given to everyrone and pursue the world which I want.
About Artwork During the COVID-19 pandemic, our communication is blocked by masks. Masks not only block viruses, but also block the acceptance of information from person to person.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona</title>
      <link>/posts/corona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/corona/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Olga Niekrasova
About Artwork This project was done in isolation, and it&amp;rsquo;s a reflection on the rapid change in our environment due to coronavirus. My message here is more than clear. In this work and in the entire series, I examined various aspects of my new lifestyle and created photographs and collages from improvised materials that I found at home. In addition, it was interesting for me to trace through objects how some of them (masks, gloves, toilet paper) became luxury objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona Tea Time</title>
      <link>/posts/coronateatime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/coronateatime/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Sarah Addouh
Introduction Sarah Addouh is an architect and collage artist based in Morocco, Casablanca.
About Artwork Sarah Addouh took this series of photos during the lockdown in Morocco. It represents sharing while respecting social distancing due to the pandemic. It also shows how we have to be careful in every single task we have to do like serving food or a glass of tea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona Time</title>
      <link>/posts/coronatime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/coronatime/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Zheng Fang
Introduction Zheng Fang was the youngest person in the world. As the cofounder of 夹山改梁, Zheng Fang starts his journey in the nexus of interactive installation, game design, generative art, performance, experimental video, painting, experimental theater, curation, and education, etc.
After graduating from the Printmaking Department of Central Academy of Fine Arts in 2018, he is now a graduate student majoring in Design | Media Arts, UCLA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID</title>
      <link>/posts/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/covid/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Berna Gulbey
Introduction Berna Gulbey has about 50 paintings so far for her COVÄ°D collection.
About Artwork In my COVID series I am aiming to show the effect of this Virus on people from all walks of life, it aims to put a full stop in that moment of time and freezes the emotion of the moment in history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid Artifact</title>
      <link>/posts/covidartifact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/covidartifact/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: James Gouldthorpe
Introduction I have always been drawn to narrative and even at its most abstract my work suggests a plot. I have found that referencing a story is an effective way to explore my own particular conceptual ideas, and a compelling way to engage an audience. Painting one image often does not fully express the ideas I am exploring, but painting several images and thoughtfully juxtaposing them next each other they begin to create their own visual language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Die for What</title>
      <link>/posts/dieforwhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dieforwhat/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Big Rex
Introduction Big Rex is a graphic designer based in Peru. He tries to create and communicate a message of reflection through a stance towards what he sees every day. His ideas are based on playing different stories that take place in the same space in parallel time. His artwork is full of very unique surreal characters which are inspired by everyday life situations, experiences, old magazines, storybooks and ideas about what the future will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Princesses</title>
      <link>/posts/disneyprincesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/disneyprincesses/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Patricia Benedicto Martínez
Introduction Patricia is a professional artist and illustrator based in Alicante, Spain.
About Artwork </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distortions</title>
      <link>/posts/distortions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/distortions/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Tianai Zhang
About Artwork Subway,bathroom,bedroom,news in pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Want Cotton Candy?</title>
      <link>/posts/doyouwantcottoncandy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/doyouwantcottoncandy/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Kimberly Giselle
Introduction My work consists of photographing the beauty of nature, capturing the world through my perspective. Nature is peaceful, yet calming to me as it is expressed throughout my work. Although my images depict green sceneries, the desert is also intriguing to me by its appealing view of the silky warm sand. My photographs often reveal the ravishing structure of mother earth, traveling to different locations across California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreakuri Yumi</title>
      <link>/posts/dreakuriyumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dreakuriyumi/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Andi Zhang
Introduction: Andi is an artist graduated from Central Academy of Fine Arts in China.
About Artwork The work originated from my fear of pandemics and other diseases, drawing on the image of virus-infected cells, cancer cells, blood vessels, and gas masks, and giving the work a &amp;ldquo;breathing&amp;rdquo; effect through programming and new conductive materials. I hope to express the things I fear and the process of defeating my fears in the form of beauty, embodying my own artistic view of life and death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Closed</title>
      <link>/posts/earthclosed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/earthclosed/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Rajiv Fernandez</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>East Coast</title>
      <link>/posts/eastcoast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/eastcoast/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Victor (Haotian) Wang
Introduction Victor is an Indie/Alternative singer-songwriter and producer from NYU, hometown being Shanghai and Yunnan in China.
About Artwork The idea of East Coast first came to my mind while flying from Shanghai to New York. At that time, my goal was to just write a song about the airport, this place full with farewells and reunions.
This pandemic is full with hustles, unexpectedness, and movements international students or foreigners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emotions</title>
      <link>/posts/emotions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/emotions/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Mehmet Akif ÖZDAL
About Artwork </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduation 2020</title>
      <link>/posts/graduation2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/graduation2020/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Yaning Zhu
About Artwork   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GUARD</title>
      <link>/posts/guard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/guard/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Icy Lu
Introduction: Icy is a 17-year-old second year undergraduate international student in Los Angeles.
About Artwork This poster was finished in early 2021. In the picture, a doctor with tired eyes silently guards a little girl with his wings. Our current easy life comes from these people who dedicate themselves silently and don&amp;rsquo;t ask for rewards are bearing the burden for us. The tired eyes of the doctor, the faint wrinkles between the eyebrows and the puffiness all revealed the menacing force of the pandemic and the hard work of the medical staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Indoors</title>
      <link>/posts/happyindoors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/happyindoors/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: April Ding
Introduction April Ding is a recent UCLA graduate. She is a visual/Interactive Experience Designer.
About Artwork In Spring 2020, many states in the US imposed lockdowns due to the impact of the Covid-19 pandemic. While some people find comfort at home, most others struggle with limited human interactions. More people around me were having more downtimes than before, and that was when I decided to make something that help people discover the little happy moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homie</title>
      <link>/posts/homie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/homie/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Laura Grombone
Introduction Laura is an undergraduate student at UCLA.
About Artwork This painting titled &amp;ldquo;Homie&amp;rdquo; was inspired by the emotions I felt during this time that led me to question what “home” meant to me. It is a big painting (40’’ x 40’’) and was done with oil paints in a plywood board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I AM FINE, AND YOU</title>
      <link>/posts/iamfineandyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/iamfineandyou/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Danyang Song
Introduction I’m Danyang, an artist based on ceramics. My works involve modern ceramics, industrial design and new media art. The topics I explored include individual emotion and feelings, culture conflict and social issues. The material of ceramics plays a key role in my works. Other materials, covering wood and metal, are also included. Ceramics, as a traditional Chinese material, inspire me to create works to reflect Chinese culture, meanwhile, it also encourages me to explore various possibilities of ceramics in modern art and combination with other mediums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Want To Go Outside</title>
      <link>/posts/iwanttogooutside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/iwanttogooutside/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Hanxiao Yang
About Artwork Let the ballons go outdoor for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Survive</title>
      <link>/posts/justsurvive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/justsurvive/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Ellen Lee
About Artwork My piece &amp;ldquo;Just Survive&amp;rdquo; is about how it&amp;rsquo;s enough to simply live. In our society, being productive is seen as our only goal in life. We place so much of our self worth on productivity whether that is with academics, self care, etc. This is one of the reasons why the corona virus pandemic has had such a huge effect on many people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyworker Masks</title>
      <link>/posts/keyworkermasks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/keyworkermasks/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Freyja Sewell
About Artwork Facemask is 2020’s most iconic and important visual motif. It has moved from being a simple piece of PPE to a badge of honour, worn by the heroes who have kept our society functioning during the most disruptive collective experience since World War II. Artists and designers are using this motif within their work to help reframe our perception, its inclusion in stunning images and positive narratives encourages the daily use of them by the public, a critical step in shaping our choices moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Downtown During the Pandemic</title>
      <link>/posts/ladowntownduringthepandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ladowntownduringthepandemic/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Bozhi Wu
 Bozhi is a current UCLA third-year student.
About Artwork This set of photos were taken during the pandemic in LA downtown. The photographer captured various kinds of life stories during this difficult time, especially the ones for the homeless, the poor, and the workers. Through this set of photography, the photographer was trying to record the most authentic emotions people were having during the pandemic, and elicit people’s reflections toward various aspects of their own life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lexie: A Tale During Covid</title>
      <link>/posts/lexieataleduringcovid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/lexieataleduringcovid/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Yingru Huang
Introduction Yingru is a senior stutent in UCLA. She started dancing at the age of five, after her parents enrolled her into her local ballet studio, hoping that she will gain some lifelong skills that will carry into her future. What they didn¡¯t expect, however, was for her to genuinely pursue dance full-heartedly as both artistic and academic realms of study. After being given dance and choreographic opportunities throughout high school, Yingru affirmed her love for dance as an expressionist medium and studied under UCLA¡¯s World Arts and Culture/Dance department to further explore and research her artistic whims.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London</title>
      <link>/posts/london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/london/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Jun Pu
About Artwork </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masker</title>
      <link>/posts/masker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/masker/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Wei Huang
Introduction Wei Huang received his bachelor degree at the Central Academy of Fine Arts (CAFA) in China, class of 2020, and his master degree at University of the Arts, London, class of 2022.
About Artwork What&amp;rsquo;s dividing people is not solely the physical separation caused by face masks, but the doubt and feature behind the masks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More PPE Now</title>
      <link>/posts/moreppenow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/moreppenow/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Mildred Grace German
Introduction Mildred Grace German is a Filipino-Canadian multidisciplinary artist based on the unceded Coast Salish Territories of the Musqueam, Squamish, and Tsleil-Waututh Nations.
About Artwork &amp;ldquo;It was nearly a wipe out of parts of the working class, as nurses, and workers scrambled to find N95, and PPEs. Where were the unions and government agencies in securing these PPE supplies for the workers and the masses, as news of the coronavirus spread months before the lockdown?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Date in Quarantine</title>
      <link>/posts/dateinquarantine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dateinquarantine/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Yumeng Zhuang
Introduction Yumeng is part of UCLA Class of 2021, an art lover majoring in Physics.
About Artwork In the United States, it has been about ten months since the quarantine threw our lives out of the familiar track. I think my relationships with other people suffered the most, and many people started to have pets to fill in the blanks and welcome them as part of their families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCC (Non-contact Container)</title>
      <link>/posts/ncc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ncc/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Ruizhi Xiao
About Artwork Based on the actual situation in China during the epidemic, this work ponders what will affect people when the disaster comes. The living habits of contemporary people have made people inseparable from modern logistics. During the epidemic, the increasingly high reward amount for couriers and the trend that everything is available for takeout make me reconsider the possibility of modern logistics. Based on the above situation, I designed this &amp;ldquo;NCC&amp;rdquo;, which takes the family as the unit to realize contactless logistics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Fossils</title>
      <link>/posts/pandemicfossils/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pandemicfossils/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Ken Goldman
Introduction Ken Goldman is an artist based in Israel. His art is filled with insider references innuendos and humor. While at times seemingly irreverent - the works are inspired by and react to; traditional, texts, and rituals. He sees his art as a vehicle for promoting dialogue, a catalyst for provoking people into re-evaluating their preconceptions, a medium for breaking down stereotypes, and an opportunity for people of all walks of life to connect with theirs and others&#39; religion, culture, and history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Poetry</title>
      <link>/posts/pandemicpoetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pandemicpoetry/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Cheyanne Mclaurin
Introduction Cheyanne Mclaurin is a port based in Los Angeles, California. She is also currently study at University of California, Los Angeles, as the Class of 2024. For personal interests, Cheyanne loves eating, sightseeing, and working out.
About Artwork The following poems were inspired by the roller coaster of emotions that I and many others have faced during the pandemic. They focus mainly on the ups and down of isolation as well as the process of adjusting to our new world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandemonium</title>
      <link>/posts/pandemonium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pandemonium/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Elisabeth Koch
Introduction Elisabeth Koch is a PhD student in Iranian Studies and Egyptology at UCLA, the model her boyfriend, who consented to the submission of this picture despite him sporting a pandemic haircut.
About Artwork This picture was taken in the catacombs of Kom el-Shoqafa in Alexandria, Egypt. It captures the ominous atmosphere that has infused every day life during the pandemic. Death has become as omnipresent as it is in the catacombs, which are part of the necropolis of ancient Alexandria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pickled Stripper - Life Through Pickled Color Glasses</title>
      <link>/posts/pickledstripper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pickledstripper/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Kayla Tange
Introduction: Kayla Tange was born in South Korea and adopted by a Japanese American family. Her love for poetry and photography slowly progressed into a conceptual performance practice which incorporates elements of exotic dancing. Physical and psychic boundaries, sexuality and permanence are also recurring themes. She often uses dark comedy in her performance work to explore love and longing, societal taboos and catharsis. She is the co-producer of Sacred Wounds, a show around ritual, subverting cultural stereotypes and ancestral healing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playground</title>
      <link>/posts/playground/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/playground/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Hugo Greenhill
About Artwork </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postcard To 2021 From 2020</title>
      <link>/posts/postcardto2021from2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/postcardto2021from2020/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Ella Liu
Introduction Ella Liu was born in 1997 in Guangdong, China, and moved to the US in 2016. In 2019, she got her Associate degree at Mt.San Antonio College. She’s now a senior student at the University of California, Berkeley. She works in digital painting, painting, and photography. She has participated in a cookbook design, package design, and an app’s artistic design. Her work captures the drama of pop culture icons and figures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protests</title>
      <link>/posts/protests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/protests/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Joshua Windsor
Introduction Originally from New Zealand, I developed a passion for photography during a year-long trip to South America. Since then, I relocated to London and undertook a masters degree in philosophy and now work full-time as a travel photographer. With travel currently hindered due to COVID-19, I have turned my lens to documenting the social impact of the pandemic and related protests.
About Artwork Descriptions are in the order of the photos below</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quiet Fires and Silent Cries</title>
      <link>/posts/quietfiresandsilentcries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/quietfiresandsilentcries/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Fiona Hsu
Introduction Fiona Hsu was born in February of 2001 in Orange County, California. At the age of five, her artistic journey ignited when her mother encourages her to make paper dolls instead of playing with cheap plastic toys. As she became better with her hands, her paper friends inspired her to keep creating. And so a passion for art ignited. She started drawing and painting on her own ever since, and during her recovery from a foot tendon surgery back in 2015, she developed blazing passion for fine art photography at the age of fourteen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle</title>
      <link>/posts/seattle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/seattle/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Aaron Zhang
Introduction Aaron Zhang is a junior international student studying at UCSD. In his spare time, he enjoys photography, aerial photography, and video editing.
About Artwork In the first half of the year, the epidemic broke out. Overnight, major cities in the United States seemed to pause. Even during peak hours of traffic congestion in downtown Seattle, there is only a few vehicles on I-5. The Hyatt Hotel in downtown Seattle ceased operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelter Made from Metal Net</title>
      <link>/posts/sheltermadefrommetalnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sheltermadefrommetalnet/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Stefania
Introduction Stefania graduated from the Academia Belle Arti Di Brera
About Artwork Masks increased our distance with each other. Our hearts are as if encircled by metal nets. The color red represents sunshine, passion, love and hope. With this blooming red flower, a sign of hope is coming our way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stay Strong</title>
      <link>/posts/staystrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/staystrong/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Erin O&amp;rsquo;Neil
Introduction Erin is a pre-math major at UCLA. I have created art for as long as I can remember and will continue to pursue it as a hobby during college. I love to use acrylic paints but also enjoy mediums such as charcoal and watercolor.
About Artwork Stay Strong depicts the exhaustion of frontline workers who are waiting for relief. They are working tirelessly to provide care for sick people during the seemingly endless pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop Worrying</title>
      <link>/posts/stopworrying/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/stopworrying/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Riiko Sakkinen
Introduction Riiko Sakkinen is a visual artist and political dissident. He is the founder of Turborealism, an anti-capitalist art movement. Sakkinen was born in 1976 in Helsinki. He lives in Spain since 2003 and is headquartered in Pepino, Province of Toledo. Sakkinen studied at the Academy of Fine Arts, Helsinki, graduating in 2002.
About Artwork The complete title of the work is called &amp;ldquo;How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Corona Virus,&amp;rdquo; which comes from the film Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Heroes | How NOT to Use Masks</title>
      <link>/posts/superheroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/superheroes/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Javier Pérez Estrella
Introduction Javier Pérez Estrella is a 35 years old artist from Ecuador.
About Artwork How NOT to Use Masks A funny guide of how NOT to use masks in pandemic.
Super Heroes During the quarantine, he created these illustrations to pay tribute to doctors around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Precaution</title>
      <link>/posts/takingprecaution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/takingprecaution/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Jessica Till
Introduction Jessica Till is a contemporary artist that utilizes various software applications and immersive processes to explore issues of identity. Her passion for digital photography, experimental projection lighting, graphic design, and typography helps her explore social roles and interactions between technology and humanity.
About Artwork In a world where disinformation is more viral than Covid-19 itself, it is important to take all the necessary precautions to protect yourself and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Only Staircase To Get Up Is Each Other</title>
      <link>/posts/eachother/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/eachother/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Jose Simonovis
Introduction I was born in Venezuela in 1993 and completed my studies in Architecture and Design at the University of Los Andes, ULA. During my architecture career, I discovered an important interest in Arts, especially Visual Arts. So I started to explore myself in conceptual photography. As a consequence I also started to post and express my thoughts and feelings about my personal living situations or global situations like in this case that we all are put in one, in a pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The privilege of quarantine 2020</title>
      <link>/posts/theprivilegeofquarantine2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/theprivilegeofquarantine2020/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Luciana Acuña
Introduction Luciana Acuña is an art historian from Argentina, who is also developing photo-documentary and photojournalism that works independently. She also has consolidated experience as a curator and content writer in different national and international media for more than ten years.
About Artwork The current situation in the context of a pandemic led to the fact that, faced with the obligation of compulsory isolation, the structural inequality of my country became evident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sense of Distance - A Production Line of the Shelter</title>
      <link>/posts/thesenseofdistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/thesenseofdistance/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Shiyu Huang
About Artwork Shiyu went to the west of Sichuan, China in August 2020. At that time, the pandemic was well controlled, so people tended to pull down the mask and hang it over their chins to breathe the fresh air in the remote mountains. However, Shiyu saw that when people encountered strangers or unfamiliar places, they still wore the mask to show a &amp;ldquo;safe distance&amp;rdquo; from the strangeness and a &amp;ldquo;sense of crisis&amp;rdquo; towards the unknown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOUCH</title>
      <link>/posts/touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/touch/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Marissa Bennett
Introduction Marissa Bennett is a multidisciplinary designer based in Los Angeles, California. She specializes in graphic design, illustration, and photography. Marissa recently completed her final year working towards a Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Design Media Arts with a minor in Global Studies at the University of California Los Angeles (UCLA) in June 2020.
About Artwork This work is a revisitation and analysis of images taken while I was living in Italy during the beginning of the COVID-19 outbreak, with an emphasis on photos from a weekend trip to Venice on February 22, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncanny</title>
      <link>/posts/uncanny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/uncanny/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Yuying Song
Introduction Yuying Song is currently in Valencia, Spain. She is pursuing a Doctoral degree in Art Production and Research, at the Polytechnic University of Valencia.
About Artwork Affected by the covid-19 epidemic, people&amp;rsquo;s lifestyles has been changed, alcohol and masks have become necessities in people&amp;rsquo;s daily lives. Keeping a safe social distance in public has become the norm in people&amp;rsquo;s lives. Living in isolation and social distance can also make people feel lonely and uneasy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus Body</title>
      <link>/posts/virusbody/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/virusbody/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Moham Wang
Introduction Moham Wang is an MFA CalArts student originally from Moham.
About Artwork This work is a visualization of my dreams during the pandemic period. The installation demonstrates the nature of chaotic dreams while maintaining a sense of balance and connection amidst all the fractures. As a whole, the work is a human body whose “skin,” the canvas paper, is penetrated and connected simultaneously by electronic wires resembling blood vessels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus Go Away</title>
      <link>/posts/virusgoaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/virusgoaway/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Liuzhen Su
Introduction Liuzhen is a PhD student at the Fudan University in China. His personal website is coolionet.cn.
About Artwork This photo was taken at Zhuzhou city in China on March 19th, 2020. The words are written in Chinese, whose direct translation would be &amp;ldquo;Virus Go Away&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP: Student Perspectives on COVID-19</title>
      <link>/posts/wakeupstudentperspectivesoncovid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/wakeupstudentperspectivesoncovid-19/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Geneva Hines
Introduction Geneva Hines is a media production student from Ryerson University, Toronto, Ontario.
About Artwork Created in summer 2020, the WAKE UP: Student Perspectives On COVID-19 Documentary includes the contributions of 34 students from 12 different countries, representing five continents. The documentary highlights the degree of impact the novel virus has had on a wide range of students.
As COVID-19 has taken the world by storm, one thing has grown increasingly apparent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Without Us</title>
      <link>/posts/withoutus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/withoutus/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Federico Clapis
Introduction: Federico Clapis is a sculpture artist from Milan, Italy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xi Wei</title>
      <link>/posts/xiwei/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/xiwei/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Yihua He
Introduction Yihua is a student from Fudan University in China.
About Artwork This is a story set in the context of the beginning of the coronavirus outbreak in China.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoom Fatigue</title>
      <link>/posts/zoomfatigue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/zoomfatigue/</guid>
      <description>About Author Artist Name: Kiani Wish
Introduction Kiani Wish is a transfer senior student majoring in Digital Media Arts at UCLA. They enjoy sleeping, internet surfing, and making the most of their time at home.
About Artwork Zoom fatigue, a new phenomenon emerging from overuse within virtual platforms, is very real. Symptoms of this digital distraction include worry, tiredness, and burnout. Being a UCLA student still engaged in the intensity of the quarter system and managing several classes during a pandemic has made us spend days inside our screens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN CALL「Impressions COVID」Online Art Exhibition</title>
      <link>/posts/impressions-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 12:45:05 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/impressions-covid/</guid>
      <description>Important Dates Submission Deadline: January 24th, 2021
Exhibition Opening: February 15th, 2021
Exhibition Portal: 「Impressions COVID」
 About This Exhibit Teeming with natural disasters, domestic and international social tensions, these past few months hardly left us with a mental break.
As a student organization founded amidst the pandemic, we hope to provide a safe space for all to share their perspectives and to document the different experiences in this special time, from the US and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
